http://www.northwesthandmade.com/privacy-policy

Our ProductsAccessoriesArmoiresBedsBenchesBookcasesChairs & BarstoolsDesksDining TablesDressersEntertainment CentersHutchesMirrorsNightstandsTablesCommercial SalesOur LinesBlue PineRusticSelkirkTimberTrestle CreekPhoto GalleryCustom Furniture GalleryTimber Furniture GalleryRustic Furniture GalleryBlue Pine Furniture GalleryCommercial Furniture GalleryArtistsFeatured ArtistsVideosAbout UsAbout UsOur LocationShippingContact UsCall 877-880-1962 or (208) 255-1962Email Us
MenuOur ProductsAccessoriesArmoiresBedsBenchesBookcasesChairs & BarstoolsDesksDining TablesDressersEntertainment CentersHutchesMirrorsNightstandsTablesCommercial SalesOur LinesBlue PineRusticSelkirkTimberTrestle CreekPhoto GalleryCustom Furniture GalleryTimber Furniture GalleryRustic Furniture GalleryBlue Pine Furniture GalleryCommercial Furniture GalleryArtistsFeatured ArtistsVideosAbout UsAbout UsOur LocationShippingContact UsMenuPrivacy policyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on August 6th 2013Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the contact link here.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:1. To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)2. To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)3. To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)4. To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.5. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature6. To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.
